#### 1 ####
Controls: Search Mode{end}

#### 2 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}In this mode, your character moves through the
world, picks up items etc.
                        - Movement -

Walking: Move {0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E00B}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0} to walk.

Running: Hold down {0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E022}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0} to run in the direction
you are facing.

Strafing: Hold down {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E011}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0} and move {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E00B}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0} to strafe.
{0E:3:0:2:1}                    - Camera Controls -

Looking Around: Move {0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E00C}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Centering: Press {0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E00F}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

{0E:3:0:2:1}                      - Search Controls -

Focus: Hold down {0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E023}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Touching Objects: Hold down {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E023}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0} next to
the object you want to touch.

Interaction: Press {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E007}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Switch to Photo Mode: Press {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E005}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.{end}

#### 3 ####
How to play in Search Mode, the mode used when
exploring the game world.{end}

#### 4 ####
Controls: Photo Mode{end}

#### 5 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}In this mode, you operate the Camera Obscura.

                  - Camera Controls 1 -

Changing Position: Move about by using {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E00B}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Changing Focus: Move the camera using {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E00C}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0},
or {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E01E}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0} if {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E01E}{E012}{E00C}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF} is set in General Settings.
{0E:3:0:2:1}                   - Camera Controls 2 -

Quick Focus Change: Hold down {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E011}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}
and move {0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E00C}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Changing Angle: Move {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E01E}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.
{0E:3:0:2:1}                    - Taking Photos 1 -

Shooting: Press the shutter with {0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E010}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Locking On: To lock on to {0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E026}{0E:4:0:2:CD}, hold down {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E022}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Changing Film: Switch films using {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E017}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.
{0E:3:0:2:1}                    - Taking Photos 2 -

Changing Lenses: Switch lenses using {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E016}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.

Special Shots: Press {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E013}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0} to activate
a lens's ability.

Switch to Search Mode: Press {0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CD}{0E:4:0:2:1CD}{E005}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:1:2:0}.{end}

#### 6 ####
How to play in Photo Mode, the mode used when you are taking pictures
with the Camera Obscura.{end}

#### 7 ####
{end}

#### 8 ####
Yuri Kozukata{end}

#### 9 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A young girl with psychic abilities. After
surviving a tragic accident, she has been able to
see ghosts and visions of the past. Since that day
she has felt death calling to her.

One day she disappeared, and Hisoka was asked
to find her.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Hisoka found Yuri just as she was about to jump
from a cliff. Yuri now stays with Hisoka at her
antiques shop.

Yuri avoids other people, terrified of seeing into
their souls. She helps around the shop, mostly by
cleaning. She rarely deals with customers.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She has always found it hard to ignore those in
need, and her abilities only make things worse.

The only time she feels free of her worries is
when she cycles.{end}

#### 10 ####
About Yuri Kozukata{end}

#### 11 ####
Yuri Kozukata - 2{end}

#### 12 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}After losing all her family in a tragic accident,
she gained the ability to glance into people's
souls and read their thoughts. Doctors thought it
was just shock, and that she would heal in time.
She slowly became withdrawn, isolated.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Haunted by images of death, Yuri saw only one
way out. Fixated with the idea that everyone dies
alone, she tried to jump off a cliff. Hisoka got to
her just in time, and told her that if she really
wanted it, then they could die together. Yuri has
been staying with Hisoka at her shop ever since.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The roles were reversed when Yuri had to find
the missing Hisoka. Yuri never could ignore
those in need.

In the end she felt a kinship to Ose, after
glancing the souls of the dead on Mt. Hikami.
The Black Water calls to her.{end}

#### 13 ####
About Yuri Kozukata - 2{end}

#### 14 ####
Hisoka Kurosawa{end}

#### 15 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The owner of an antiques store, she has
developed her psychic abilities by learning
from local elders, and by researching the subject.

One of those locals gave her a Camera Obscura,
which she now uses to look for missing objects
and people.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She stopped Yuri from jumping, and brought the
orphan girl back to her shop.

She feels for Yuri, but Hisoka doesn't have the
power she does. She can only sense the ghosts
and memories, not see them.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She tells fortunes as a hobby. She has become
quite popular with the young students who
frequent her café. Her coffee is renowned for its
taste, and Hisoka likes to say,

"Sometimes a cup of coffee
can make all the difference."{end}

#### 16 ####
About Hisoka Kurosawa{end}

#### 17 ####
Hisoka Kurosawa - 2{end}

#### 18 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The owner of an antiques store, she has
developed her shadow reading ability by learning
from local elders, and by researching the subject.

One of those locals gave her a Camera Obscura,
which she now uses to look for missing objects
and people.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She stopped Yuri from jumping, and brought the
orphan girl back to her shop.

She feels for Yuri, but Hisoka doesn't have the
power she does. She can only sense the ghosts
and memories, not see them.
{0E:3:0:2:1}On a missing person case, the girl she was
looking for committed suicide before she could
get to her. Hisoka was left broken, and she took
on no more missing person cases.

Until Miu, that is. Moved by her foster mother's
pleas, she went to look for her.
{0E:3:0:2:1}When she saw Yuri on the cliff, memories of the
girl she couldn't save came flooding back and,
overcome with emotion, she rushed to stop Yuri
from jumping.

The Maidens of Black Water called for Hisoka to
join them, but in the end Yuri saved her.{end}

#### 19 ####
About Hisoka Kurosawa - 2{end}

#### 20 ####
Ren Hojo{end}

#### 21 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A writer, known for basing his novels on
real events. He is very thorough in his research.

He also writes cheap pulp fiction under a
pen name in between projects. He acts on
intuition, and has a laissez-faire attitude.
{0E:3:0:2:1}He asked Hisoka to find Postmortem
Photographs for a new book he's writing. Hisoka
has helped him before to find other reference
materials, such as old curios and books.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren has been haunted by the memory of killing
a girl in some kind of ceremony, and by
recurring dreams of the girl looking back at him.

For this reason, he's always felt uneasy around
women, especially when they look him in the
eye.{end}

#### 22 ####
About Ren Hojo{end}

#### 23 ####
Ren Hojo - 2{end}

#### 24 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A relative of Dr. Aso. Amongst the Postmortem
Photographs he asked Hisoka to find is a photo
of Ose Kurosawa.

The photo awakes within Ren the feelings
Dr. Aso had for Ose, and so he gets involved in
the events taking place on Mt. Hikami.
{0E:3:0:2:1}As a boy, Ren found a bundle of white hair in
his family's storeroom. Upon touching it, he
glanced Dr. Aso's memory of killing a
young girl.

Tracing Dr. Aso's footsteps to Mt. Hikami, he
gets involved in a Ghost Marriage and must
choose between two brides.{end}

#### 25 ####
About Ren Hojo - 2{end}

#### 26 ####
Rui Kagamiya{end}

#### 27 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren's live-in assistant, recommended to him by
his publisher. Once hired, Rui moved in and
took charge of preparing reference materials
for Ren's books, as well as other secretarial tasks.

It was a relief for Ren, who finds such things
tedious.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui is well-organized and well-mannered, but
will scold Ren if he gets too untidy.

Rui has now taken over the house chores as well.
Ren has started to rely on Rui so much that he'd
be lost if he ever went back to living alone.{end}

#### 28 ####
About Rui Kagamiya{end}

#### 29 ####
Rui Kagamiya - 2{end}

#### 30 ####
Joining Ren as his assistant, Rui found herself
on Mt. Hikami. The investigation proved more
dangerous than anyone suspected, and she was
spirited away.

After being rescued by Ren, Rui feels a deep
desire to always be by his side.{end}

#### 31 ####
About Rui Kagamiya - 2{end}

#### 32 ####
Miu Hinasaki{end}

#### 33 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu went to Mt. Hikami to look for her mother,
and then disappeared without a trace.

Since she was little, she has had the ability to see
ghosts and read the thoughts of people she
touched.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Her ability allows her to see how insincere
people can be, making her distrustful and afraid
of her own power.

She's cold towards everyone, but misses her
mother, who she thinks will be the only
person out there who might understand.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu ran away from her foster mother to follow
the trace of her mother to Mt. Hikami.

She works as an actress, and has appeared in a
few shows, but she mainly works as a model for
magazines.{end}

#### 34 ####
About Miu Hinasaki{end}

#### 35 ####
Miu Hinasaki - 2{end}

#### 36 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu's strong shadow reading abilities are a
hallmark of the Hinasaki bloodline. Miu is a
Shadowborn, a child of a human and a ghost.
She was raised by the Iyamas ever since Miku
went missing when Miu was only
three years old.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu can read other people's thoughts by
touching them, so she has always been aware
that her foster family only took care of her
because they pity her.

She went to look for the only person she felt
would understand: her mother.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu's ability to read people's minds makes her
act coldly towards others, and even look down
on them.

She would like to get closer to Yuri, who has the
same ability as her, but after years of shutting
people out, it's difficult for her to open up.
{0E:3:0:2:1}After saving her mother, they could finally say to
each other all the things they've wanted to say
over the years.{end}

#### 37 ####
About Miu Hinasaki - 2{end}

#### 38 ####
Fuyuhi Himino{end}

#### 39 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}After coming to Hisoka for help, she went to
look for her friend, Haruka Momose, on
Mt. Hikami by herself.

Fuyuhi was one of Hisoka's regulars. Not in the
café, but for the fortunetelling. She hasn't come
lately, so Yuri doesn't know her.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Hisoka did not accept the case right away, but
asked for some time to think about it.

Growing impatient, Fuyuhi visited the shop.{end}

#### 40 ####
About Fuyuhi Himino{end}

#### 41 ####
Fuyuhi Himino - 2{end}

#### 42 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A girl who asked Hisoka to find her friend,
Haruka Momose. Hisoka asked for some time to
think about it.

Growing impatient, Fuyuhi visited the shop and
saw that Hisoka was not there. She decided to
go to Mt. Hikami and search for her friend
on her own.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Fuyuhi and Haruka had once attempted a group
suicide with three other girls, but they survived.

They made a promise to die together, so Fuyuhi
was certain that Haruka wouldn't have gone to
commit suicide without her.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri found her on Mt. Hikami, but Fuyuhi cut
her own throat under the influence of a ghost.

The last thing she saw before dying was a
kimono-clad woman who had also slit her throat
and a shrine maiden with her eyes covered.{end}

#### 43 ####
About Fuyuhi Himino - 2{end}

#### 44 ####
Haruka Momose{end}

#### 45 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}One of the people listed in Hisoka's missing
persons file. Hisoka was asked to find her by
Fuyuhi Himino, who later committed suicide.

According to Fuyuhi, Haruka was last seen near
Mt. Hikami.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Haruka goes to the same school as Fuyuhi. She
was also often seen getting her fortune told in
Hisoka's shop. She's never met Yuri.

She's a kind and timid girl, easily influenced by
others. She only started coming to shop because
of her friends.
{0E:3:0:2:1}After attempting suicide with a group of her
friends, only she and Fuyuhi survived.{end}

#### 46 ####
About Haruka Momose{end}

#### 47 ####
Haruka Momose - 2{end}

#### 48 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}One of the girls spirited away to Mt. Hikami.
Yuri found her in a reliquary submerged in the
water in the Womb Cavern and brought her back
to the shop, only to see her disappear again.
Like Fuyuhi, a ghost brought her to the world of
the dead.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She was a very kind girl, happy to follow the
crowd. She went along with everything her
friends did, including a failed group suicide.

She could sense the pain and sorrow of her dead
friends. Unable to stand it, she went to
Mt. Hikami to die.
{0E:3:0:2:1}It seems that, just like before, she has been put
in a reliquary. Only this time, there will be no
escape.{end}

#### 49 ####
About Haruka Momose - 2{end}

#### 50 ####
Kunihiko Aso{end}

#### 51 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A 19th Century scientist. He was interested in
the invisible, the intangible, such as ghosts and
the Netherworld. His research led him to
construct the Camera Obscura, a camera capable
of photographing things not of the world of the
living.
{0E:3:0:2:1}He was an outcast in the scientific community
and few of his research papers remain.

He made several Camera Obscuras, misplacing
some, and entrusting others to his friends. His
cameras are highly sought-after antiques.{end}

#### 52 ####
About Kunihiko Aso{end}

#### 53 ####
Kunihiko Aso - 2{end}

#### 54 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Kunihiko grew up in a town near Mt. Kagiroi.

There he befriended the young shrine maiden,
Shiragiku. She was chosen to be sent to
Mt. Hikami as a sacrifice. Kunihiko was tasked
with obtaining a lock of her hair as a token
during the sacrificial ceremony.
{0E:3:0:2:1}After becoming a scientist he traveled
all over, photographing the places he visited and
the people he met.

The residents of Mt. Hikami invited him to
photograph the shrine maidens, as his Camera
Obscura was rumored to capture the souls of the
subjects.
{0E:3:0:2:1}He took a photo of Ose Kurosawa, and just as
she stole his heart, he trapped hers in a
photograph. He then left, taking her soul with
him.

He never went back, and it is unclear whether he
recalled his time with Ose Kurosawa, or his past
with Shiragiku.{end}

#### 55 ####
About Kunihiko Aso - 2{end}

#### 56 ####
Keiji Watarai{end}

#### 57 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A folklorist who was studying Mt. Hikami. His
father was English, his mother Japanese. He
moved to Japan to learn more about its folklore.

He moved to Mt. Hikami to study its history
and religion. What became of him is still
unknown.
{0E:3:0:2:1}His findings were never widely published, but
they can be found if you know where to look.

His house is now known as "the Veiled House,"
which has itself become a part of the folklore
surrounding the mountain.{end}

#### 58 ####
About Keiji Watarai{end}

#### 59 ####
Keiji Watarai - 2{end}

#### 60 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A folklorist who was studying Mt. Hikami. His
father was English, his mother Japanese. He
moved to Japan to learn more about its folklore.

Intrigued by the rituals performed on
Mt. Hikami, he moved there to study the area
in more detail.
{0E:3:0:2:1}He vanished after obtaining a photograph of a
bride. After attempts to turn the mountain into a
tourist spot failed, both he and his house were
forgotten. When the mountain gained infamy,
the house, which seemed to drive people to
suicide, came to be known as
"the Veiled House."
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren found the Veiled House and followed after
Keiji's trail, only to discover that he had turned
into a ghost.

He looked rotten, and as if he had been stuck in
one of the reliquaries.{end}

#### 61 ####
About Keiji Watarai - 2{end}

#### 62 ####
Miku Hinasaki{end}

#### 63 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu Hinasaki's mother. She has been able to see
ghosts since childhood.

When she lost her brother, her only blood
relative, she moved in with her brother's friend,
and started working as his assistant.
{0E:3:0:2:1}When she got pregnant, she moved to a house
owned by an old woman she knew, and it was
there she gave birth to Miu.

She disappeared when Miu was just
three years old.{end}

#### 64 ####
About Miku Hinasaki{end}

#### 65 ####
Miku Hinasaki - 2{end}

#### 66 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu Hinasaki's mother. She has been able to see
ghosts since childhood.

When she lost her brother, her only blood
relative, she moved in with her brother's friend,
and started working as his assistant.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She got pregnant by the ghost of her beloved
and gave birth to Miu, a Shadowborn.

This all but killed Miku, so she went to
Mt. Hikami to enter into a Ghost Marriage and
become a Pillar. She did not age in the casket,
and looks more like Miu's sister.{end}

#### 67 ####
About Miku Hinasaki - 2{end}

#### 68 ####
Kazuya Sakaki{end}

#### 69 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren's friend since high school, he now works in
the city. He was helping Ren collect Postmortem
Photographs when he suddenly lost contact.

He's always had a tendency to go off on his own,
often for days, so Hisoka isn't worried about
him yet.
{0E:3:0:2:1}He is a narcissist, which has caused issues both
at work and in his private life. Hisoka has even
suggested Ren might be better off if without
him.

Kazuya never seemed the type to settle down, so
when he said he was getting married, Ren was
justifiably stunned.{end}

#### 70 ####
About Kazuya Sakaki{end}

#### 71 ####
Kazuya Sakaki - 2{end}

#### 72 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A former schoolmate of Ren's. He was collecting
Postmortem Photographs for Ren when he went
missing. Some days later he called with news of
his impending marriage.

It was a Ghost Marriage with the bride in the
photograph.
{0E:3:0:2:1}During the ceremony he was overcome with fear
of the bride, and guilt towards Ren.

The Ghost Marriage failed, and by the time Ren
found him he had turned into a ghost.{end}

#### 73 ####
About Kazuya Sakaki - 2{end}

#### 74 ####
Tsumugi Katashina{end}

#### 75 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A girl who disappeared on Mt. Hikami. Abuse
from her family has left her mute. After several
suicide attempts, she ran away.

Her physician hired Hisoka to look for her
but her family had the search dropped.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The physician is now certain that Tsumugi's
family is to blame for her disappearance.{end}

#### 76 ####
About Tsumugi Katashina{end}

#### 77 ####
Tsumugi Katashina - 2{end}

#### 78 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A girl who went missing on Mt. Hikami. Since
her mother remarried, Tsumugi suffered verbal
abuse from her family, leaving her effectively
mute.

After years of abuse she made several suicide
attempts before finally running away from home.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Before that, she ran into Ayane who was deeply
moved by the girl's anguish, and felt a close
connection to her.

Tsumugi was drawn to Mt. Hikami and there
almost died. Ayane saved her and inspired her to
face up to her family, and to believe in herself.{end}

#### 79 ####
About Tsumugi Katashina - 2{end}

#### 80 ####
Ayane{end}

#### 81 ####
A ninja prodigy of the Mugen Tenshin clan's
Hajinmon sect.

The unfortunate circumstances of her conception
led to her living her life in the shadows. She's
trying to find Tsumugi, but it is unclear why.{end}

#### 82 ####
About Ayane{end}

#### 83 ####
Akari Narumi{end}

#### 84 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A girl Hisoka had been hired to find. Hisoka did
track down the girl, but Akari killed herself by
jumping off a cliff before Hisoka could reach
her.

Traumatized, Hisoka wonders if she's to blame.
She stopped taking missing person cases after
that.{end}

#### 85 ####
About Akari Narumi{end}

#### 86 ####
Shiragiku{end}

#### 87 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}She was born in the 19th century, when
Mt. Hikami was still home to strange rituals.

She was born with psychic abilities, however she
was very frail and she was not expected to live
long. She had once been gravely ill and nearly
died, but managed to recover.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She was sent to Mt. Hikami, so that she could be
made into a Pillar. It was said that those who
were close to death could not die, and would
make for stronger Pillars.

Mt. Hikami often recruited girls from other
shrines to become Pillars.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Shiragiku chose Kunihiko Aso, her only friend,
to cut a lock of her hair as a token during a
special ceremony.

When Dr. Aso grew up, he came to think that
the surreal ceremony was just a dream.
{0E:3:0:2:1}He visited Mt. Hikami as an adult, and passed
through the Shrine of Dolls, but did not sense
Shiragiku's presence.

Shiragiku, now a Pillar deep underground,
waited for the one who had her token. Until
then, she'd play with ghosts of children killed on
Mt. Hikami.{end}

#### 88 ####
About Shiragiku{end}

#### 89 ####
Ose Kurosawa{end}

#### 90 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ose had exceptionally strong psychic abilities.
She had been chosen to be drowned in the
Shadowspring as the main Pillar of the faith.

So that she did not just disappear, she needed to
enter into a Ghost Marriage. A votive picture
was commissioned.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Rumors of Dr. Aso and his Camera Obscura,
which could capture the subject's soul, had
reached Mt. Hikami and so he was invited to
take a photo of Ose. He fell in love with her,
and she reciprocated. He then left the mountain,
taking with him a fragment of Ose's soul trapped
in the photograph.
{0E:3:0:2:1}As Ose was shut in the casket, still yearning for
Dr. Aso, Kyozo Kururugi was killing the shrine
maidens, releasing the pain and anguish they had
taken from others. Those dark thoughts entered
Ose, causing her casket to burst open and the
Black Water to flow.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The mountain was consumed by the accursed
waters. Ose, destined to endlessly relive those
shrine maidens' last moments alone in the dark,
withstood the pain for a time but she will not
last much longer.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The protective seal surrounding the mountain
has long been maintained by turning local girls
into Pillars. Ose knows that she will soon
fade, and so uses her powers to call to Yuri, a
kindred spirit, and Ren, in whom part of
Dr. Aso lives on.{end}

#### 91 ####
About Ose Kurosawa{end}

#### 92 ####
{end}

#### 93 ####
Mt. Hikami{end}

#### 94 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A 2,300ft tall mountain close to where Hisoka
and Yuri live. It used to be a holy place for a
now-dead religion, and although some of the
shrines and other buildings still stand, there are
none now alive who keep to those practices.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The mountain is blessed with natural beauty;
it overflows with springs and is overgrown
with vegetation. A company attempted to turn it
into a tourist attraction. They built new
buildings and a cable car, even printed out
brochures, but the project was abandoned after a
devastating landslide.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Mt. Hikami was once thought of as a place only
the dead could enter, and even now it attracts
those who wish to end their life. Many believe
that this notorious suicide spot is cursed.{end}

#### 95 ####
About Mt. Hikami{end}

#### 96 ####
Mikomori Hot Springs{end}

#### 97 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}An old inn that has been on Mt. Hikami for as
long as anyone remembers, it was refurbished
and made into a hot spring resort as part of the
development project. The three-floor concrete
building is a new addition.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ichiru Manor was abandoned after the old
building was lost in a massive landslide. The
owner of the inn, having lost his family,
committed suicide.

The inn is said to be haunted by the ghosts of
those who died there, including the ghost of that
ill-fated innkeeper.{end}

#### 98 ####
About Mikomori Hot Springs{end}

#### 99 ####
Kurosawa's Antiques{end}

#### 100 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}An old house renovated by Hisoka, the front hall
is now an antiques shop and café.

There was an antiques shop there to begin with,
but Hisoka always wanted to be a café owner, so
she redecorated.
{0E:3:0:2:1}There is a very relaxed atmosphere, attracting a
few regulars. Hisoka also uses it as a base for her
unusual shadow reading business.

Yet another draw for certain customers is her
fortune telling, which Hisoka does as a hobby.{end}

#### 101 ####
About Kurosawa's Antiques{end}

#### 102 ####
Pool of Purification{end}

#### 103 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A spot by the old path to the shrines on
Mt. Hikami. The path passes by a few waterfalls,
and the pilgrims used to clean themselves in their
crystal clear water before proceeding to the
shrines.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The pool below the Maiden Fall, used by shrine
maidens, was particularly beautiful. For a brief
time the Pool of Purification was a tourist
attraction, and shrine maidens performed ritual
ablutions for show, but it's been some time since
tourists last came to Mt. Hikami.
{0E:3:0:2:1}According to a legend, the true shrine maidens
of Mt. Hikami had all been murdered, which
might be the reason the faith abruptly died out.
Their bodies are said to have washed up into the
pool. Occultists like to refer to it as the
"Maiden Pool."{end}

#### 104 ####
About the Pool of Purification{end}

#### 105 ####
Unfathomable Forest{end}

#### 106 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A forest located halfway up Mt. Hikami. The
name comes from a folk tale, saying that those
who wander into the forest forget who they are
and where they are going.

The new path to the shrines goes through this
forest. It was built as part of the project aiming
to turn the mountain into a tourist destination.

{0E:3:0:2:1}However, after a landslide destroyed most of it,
only parts remain. Some areas have flooded and
are now fenced off.

Since the mountain became infamous as a suicide
spot, many curious occultists have broken
through those fences.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Belongings of missing people can be found 
there. Some say that those who go astray
in the forest do not just get lost, but that
they are killed by something.{end}

#### 107 ####
About the Unfathomable Forest{end}

#### 108 ####
Hojo Residence{end}

#### 109 ####
Ren and Rui's house. It used to be the Hojo
family's second home, but now it's just the two
of them. It's an ordinary two-story detached
house. Ren's study is on the second floor. He
spends most of his time in there, surrounded by
his books.{end}

#### 110 ####
About the Hojo Residence{end}

#### 111 ####
Shrine of Dolls{end}

#### 112 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A shrine in the Unfathomable Forest, halfway up
Mt. Hikami. A number of dolls are enshrined
there. The true purpose of the shrine has now
been forgotten, but locals all agree that it has
always been associated with dolls.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The shrine was restored for tourists and
presented as a place of doll worship. It was
abandoned after the landslide and now has a
reputation as a shrine where the ghosts of
children play. The dolls can be heard speaking,
and a white-haired girl holding a doll can be
seen staring out.{end}

#### 113 ####
About the Shrine of Dolls{end}

#### 114 ####
Womb Cavern{end}

#### 115 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}An enormous lava cave which possibly stretches
out to cover the whole area of Mt. Hikami.
Several entrances have been discovered.

Much of the cavern is flooded, so only parts are
accessible without specialist equipment.
{0E:3:0:2:1}In the past, water was deified on Mt. Hikami
and the worshippers thought of the mountain as
a divine being, with the cavern serving as its
womb. The cavern was a most sacred place, and
access to it was restricted. The entrances were
cordoned off with sacred ropes.
{0E:3:0:2:1}When the mountain was being developed for
tourism, a newly made tunnel broke through
one of the cavern walls. Water rushed into the
tunnel, drowning dozens of workers. Many
thought the disaster was brought on by a curse
incurred by disturbing such a spiritual place.{end}

#### 116 ####
About Womb Cavern{end}

#### 117 ####
Watarai Residence{end}

#### 118 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A Japanese-style house with a shingle roof, the
home of the folklorist Keiji Watarai. It had been
built on the outskirts of the Unfathomable
Forest, a place not easy to get to. Keiji likely
wanted to avoid all disturbances as he devoted
himself to studying the local religious beliefs and
practices.
{0E:3:0:2:1}When attempts to develop the mountain failed,
it was shut down. Police officers stationed at the
foot of the mountain came to investigate the
house, and found it abandoned. No one could
tell what became of the folklorist. Afterwards,
the house itself disappeared, and the whole
incident was forgotten.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Now, tales of the house have resurfaced. People
say it appears on foggy days, and that Keiji's
works will still be found in there. Others say he
is still there, continuing his research. If anyone
dares enter, then Keiji, keen to study the darker
local rituals, will kill them as sacrificial offerings.{end}

#### 119 ####
About the Watarai Residence{end}

#### 120 ####
Mt. Hikami Cable Car{end}

#### 121 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The cable car was introduced in the hopes it
would increase the number of tourists. There
are three stops on the line: Mikomori,
the Unfathomable Forest, and the Shrine of the
Ephemeral. Soon after it was opened a huge
landslide hit, and it had to be shut down.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The tourists stopped coming, and the line never
reopened. Some claim the construction work,
which involved leveling part of the mountain
and cutting a route through the forest,
desecrated the sacred ground and brought a curse
upon the line.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Nowadays fans of the occult, attracted by rumors
of ghosts seen in the empty carriages, or eerie
silhouettes of people glimpsed in the forest by
the rail track, come to take photos of the
abandoned train.{end}

#### 122 ####
About the Mt. Hikami Cable Car{end}

#### 123 ####
Hikami Tunnel{end}

#### 124 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A tunnel constructed as part of the project to
make the mountain a tourist spot. It was
supposed to go to the Twilit Peak on the
summit. As the tunnel was being dug, the
construction workers broke through to
the Womb Cavern and the tunnel flooded.
None of the workers survived.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Work on the tunnel resumed, but the
development plans for the mountain were
abandoned and the tunnel was never completed.
A road goes up to its eastern exit, but it has been
closed due to the number of trespassers who
have either died or have gone missing in and
around the tunnel.
{0E:3:0:2:1}There may still be a way to get from the tunnel
into the Womb Cavern, but the locals warn that
the ghosts of the accident victims and of shrine
maidens await any who try to find it.{end}

#### 125 ####
About Hikami Tunnel{end}

#### 126 ####
Shrine of the Ephemeral{end}

#### 127 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A large shrine near the summit of Mt. Hikami.
It is thought to have been the main shrine of the
local faith, but little is known about it. In the
brief period that the mountain was visited by
tourists, the shrine doors stood open, and people
could admire the countless lanterns in the main
hall.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The shrine was abandoned after the closure of
the cable car line. Remains of shrine maidens are
said to be found in the inner rooms. Some say
if one passes by the shrine on a foggy day, the
lanterns will be lit and a Maiden of Black Water
will be waiting.{end}

#### 128 ####
About the Shrine of the Ephemeral{end}

#### 129 ####
Forbidden Valley{end}

#### 130 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A valley near the summit of Mt. Hikami which
houses an ancient cemetery. It had been left
undisturbed until land developers decided to
create a path to the summit for the tourists. The
only way was through the Forbidden Valley.
A massive landslide flooded the valley,
destroying the path.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The graves were once exhumed in an attempt to
establish who was buried there but no bodies
were found. It is thought that the graves were
erected in memory of people who did not have
remains. Another theory is that the graves were
for the shrine maidens who were sacrificed to the
mountain.{end}

#### 131 ####
About the Forbidden Valley{end}

#### 132 ####
Twilit Peak{end}

#### 133 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}An area of land on top of Mt. Hikami, covered
in volcanic rock. It is a desolate landscape,
devoid of vegetation due to volatile gases
escaping from the rocks. Locals felt it looked like
the underworld and, along with the Lake of the
Departed, it was considered to be connected to
the Netherworld.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Locals believe it is a sacred place. A sacrificial
mound erected over a pile of caskets can be
found here, as well as the Rear Shrine of Dolls,
with dolls much older than those from the main
Shrine of Dolls, located farther down
the mountain.{end}

#### 134 ####
About the Twilit Peak{end}

#### 135 ####
Lake of the Departed{end}

#### 136 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A crater lake located on the Twilit Peak on
Mt. Hikami. The name of the lake comes from
its ghostly appearance - it is surrounded by a
white sandy beach and is always enshrouded in
mist.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Legend has it that a few times a year, when the
last rays of the setting sun reflect off the lake,
the mist clears and it becomes a link between the
worlds of the living and the dead. People living
near the mountain are advised to stay indoors on
such days, lest a calamity befall them.
{0E:3:0:2:1}However, it is also said that those seeking death
may enter the waters of the lake and cross that
dread threshold.

This may refer to the practices that were part of
the local faith. The pinwheels stuck in the sand
might have been left there by the believers to
comfort the spirits of children who crossed to
the Netherworld there.{end}

#### 137 ####
About the Lake of the Departed{end}

#### 138 ####
Hall of Fire{end}

#### 139 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The hall where the eternal Forbidden Flame was
kept. This undying fire was the source of the
flames used in local rituals.

The use of sacred flames is documented in many
religions, but those on Mt. Hikami had a unique
use for the fire.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The Forbidden Flame kept the Black Water from
pouring out of the Shadowspring. It was
necessary to carry the flame in order to safely
approach the Black Water. The Flamekeepers
in charge of tending the fire were required to
purify themselves before being allowed near it.{end}

#### 140 ####
About the Hall of Fire{end}

#### 141 ####
House of Joining{end}

#### 142 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The place where the wedding ceremonies for
shrine maidens who became Pillars were held.

The House of Joining exists between our world
and the Netherworld, and is where sacrificed
maidens were wed to men brought to the
mountain.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Only men chosen as suitable grooms could find
the house. Once inside, they would first choose a
maiden from among those whose votive pictures
were hung on the wall.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They would proceed to the Chamber of Vows,
where their chosen bride would be waiting.
Again, only the groom would be allowed into
the chamber. Afterwards, the bride would return
to her casket with the groom in tow, in order to
spend eternity there with him as a Pillar.{end}

#### 143 ####
About the House of Joining{end}

#### 144 ####
Shrine on the Water{end}

#### 145 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A shrine built on the Lake of the Departed. It
appears as if it is floating on the water's surface.
The lake feeds all the springs on the mountain
and the shrine is believed to give its blessing to
the water.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The large torii gate which marks the shrine
entrance can be seen from the shore on days
when the mist is thin. The main building was
destroyed a long time ago and nothing of it now
remains. There is supposed to be a spring under
the shrine, but its precise location is unknown.{end}

#### 146 ####
About the Shrine on the Water{end}

#### 147 ####
The Shadowspring{end}

#### 148 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A vast spring of dark water, accessible through
the Shrine on the Water.

The Black Water is said to be from the
Netherworld, to which the Shadowspring is an
entrance.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The Dark Sun hangs in the sky above,
illuminating the murky waters with its eerie
orange glow resembling the dying rays of light
at sunset. This light lures people towards it, until
they vanish into the endless dark.{end}

#### 149 ####
About the Shadowspring{end}

#### 150 ####
{end}

#### 151 ####
Camera Obscura{end}

#### 152 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A camera with the power to expose that which
normally remains hidden.

Invented by Dr. Kunihiko Aso, a researcher of
the occult. The special film it uses captures traces
of beings which are not of the world of the
living.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Several of these cameras exist, but as each was
made as a prototype their appearance and
capabilities differ. Most of them are broken now
and no one knows how to repair them.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The cameras are highly sought after by
collectors, despite rumors of them being cursed.
The collectors either see that as another unique
property and a risk worth taking, or they
discredit such talk as mere superstition.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Just like Hisoka there are people who use the
cameras as tools for specialist work. However,
such people tend to already have the ability to
sense the ephemeral. Some say that the broken
cameras aren't broken at all; the users do not
have the ability to make them work.{end}

#### 153 ####
About the Camera Obscura{end}

#### 154 ####
Postmortem Photography{end}

#### 155 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The original intention behind Postmortem
Photography was to give the mourning relatives
something to remember their loved ones by.
The bodies were dressed in the finest clothes,
and their faces made to look as if they were alive.
{0E:3:0:2:1}At a time when photographs were a luxury very
few could afford, Postmortem Photographs
offered a chance to capture an image of their
beloved. Dr. Kunihiko Aso, with his Camera
Obscura, had been invited all over Japan to take
such pictures. Most of them are on Mt. Hikami.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Postmortem Photographs were especially
treasured by those living on and around
Mt. Hikami. They believed that a camera
captures the soul of the photographed person,
preserving it unchanged for eternity.{end}

#### 156 ####
About Postmortem Photography{end}

#### 157 ####
Shadow Reading{end}

#### 158 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Shadow reading, not unlike psychometry, 
is the ability to see the "traces" related to lost
items or people who have been spirited away.
In the past, this ability was fairly common in the
Mt. Hikami area. Nowadays very few have the
knowledge necessary to perform it.

Those who still use the ability are thought to be
the descendants of Mt. Hikami shrine maidens.{end}

#### 159 ####
About shadow reading{end}

#### 160 ####
Traces{end}

#### 161 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Shadows of the past, seen when shadow reading.
Through contact with a token of the lost person
or object, a person possessing psychic abilities
can sense its trace, showing them where to go.

People with particularly strong abilities will see
the form of their quarry, and not just a shadow.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The traces will attract malevolent ghosts, so it is
dangerous to spend too long gazing at them.
Yet another risk lies in following the trace of a
person who has already died or has been
spirited away, as you may be inadvertently
following them into the world of the dead.{end}

#### 162 ####
About traces{end}

#### 163 ####
Tokens{end}

#### 164 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Tokens are used in shadow reading. They are
objects which carry a trace of a person or object
that has gone missing. 

A person with the shadow reading ability is able
to follow that trace to find that which is lost.
They can be anything: items that the subject
liked, strands of hair, letters or diaries that
mattered to them very much, or photographs,
to name a few. 
{0E:3:0:2:1}It is also possible to use items which
belonged to dead people to follow their trace to
lost or hidden items, but that kind of
shadow reading carries with it great risk.{end}

#### 165 ####
About tokens{end}

#### 166 ####
The Netherworld{end}

#### 167 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The world of the dead. It is a place of
never-ending night, permanent darkness. Where
the Netherworld connects to the world of the
living the sky glows as if in the light of the
setting sun. The light beckons those unfortunate
enough to see it towards a darkness they will
never escape.{end}

#### 168 ####
About the Netherworld{end}

#### 169 ####
Shrine Maidens{end}

#### 170 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ghosts of shrine maidens often appear on
Mt. Hikami. The shrine maidens used to look
after those who came to the mountain to end
their life. They were all murdered and became
ghosts.

There is a story that long ago the shrine maidens
were killed and their bodies washed up into the
Pool of Purification.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Now dead, they continue to
carry out their duties. Their dark gaze awakens
suicidal thoughts within any who find themselves
on Mt. Hikami.{end}

#### 171 ####
About the shrine maidens{end}

#### 172 ####
The Veiled House{end}

#### 173 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Disappearing houses have been the subject of
many folk tales and urban legends. Some say
that they hold untold riches. The Veiled House
of Mt. Hikami is a different case. It is said those
who enter it are never heard from again.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The house exists on the border between our
world and the Netherworld. The ghost of its
owner continues to haunt it and any who enter
are doomed to become trapped between worlds.{end}

#### 174 ####
About the Veiled House{end}

#### 175 ####
Effigies{end}

#### 176 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A doll in which a soul has been sealed. They
were used in rituals in lieu of real people. When
they are made to closely resemble a person, that
person's spirit is said to be transferred to the
doll. Then, should the doll be destroyed, the
person it represented will die in the same
manner.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The custom of concealing effigies that was
practiced on Mt. Hikami is said to have grim
roots. In times of famine children would be led
into the mountains to die, told that they were
playing a game. But perhaps the custom reflects
the old practice of ritual human sacrifices.{end}

#### 177 ####
About effigies{end}

#### 178 ####
Children of the Shrine{end}

#### 179 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}These were girls up to the age of seven who
served as shrine maidens. The custom of offering
a young daughter to a shrine was practiced on
Mt. Kagiroi, near Mt. Hikami.

People used to believe that the souls of young
children were not yet fully anchored in their
living bodies.
{0E:3:0:2:1}There was a saying, "The gods have your soul
until seven years old," which reflected the view
that young children's souls did not yet belong to
the material world.{end}

#### 180 ####
About the Children of the Shrine{end}

#### 181 ####
Pillars{end}

#### 182 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A long time ago in Japan, when large structures
such as bridges or castles were built, young
maidens were buried alive under the foundations
or in the walls as offerings to the gods.
{0E:3:0:2:1}These human sacrifices were believed to make
the buildings stronger and protect them from
destruction, as the maidens would forever watch
over them. They were called "Pillars," and would
support the spells and wards that kept evil
forces out of our world.{end}

#### 183 ####
About Pillars{end}

#### 184 ####
Returning to Water{end}

#### 185 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}In the Mt. Hikami faith, souls are born from the
water, so to return to it is to die.

Dying in the waters of the mountain was seen as
the right way to leave this world, and it was this
act that was known as "Returning to Water."
{0E:3:0:2:1}Only those who were seeking this death would
be permitted onto Mt. Hikami.

While it is a common belief that souls of suicides
become cursed, "Returning to Water" did not
carry that stigma and was thought to enable a
peaceful and restful death.{end}

#### 186 ####
About returning to water{end}

#### 187 ####
Glance{end}

#### 188 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The ability to glance into a person's soul, read
their mind, see their memories, and reveal their
secrets. Only those with strong shadow reading
abilities can do this, but even they will usually
only see an abstract vision of the emotions of the
people they touch.

Yuri needs physical contact to glance into
people's souls, but for especially powerful users,
they merely have to look you in the eye.{end}

#### 189 ####
About the Glance ability{end}

#### 190 ####
Pure Water{end}

#### 191 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Crystal-clear water found on Mt. Hikami.

Water was worshipped on the mountain and the
clear spring water was seen as something
extremely precious. The worshippers called it
"Pure Water."
{0E:3:0:2:1}Even during the mountain's development as a
tourist spot, those involved believed that
maintaining the high quality of the local water
would please the gods of the mountain.

According to legend, the Pure Water was the
source of life. Its opposite was the Black Water,
the source of death.{end}

#### 192 ####
About Pure Water{end}

#### 193 ####
Black Water{end}

#### 194 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Old tales from Mt. Hikami speak of Black Water,
the waters of death which poured out from the
Netherworld. It was the dark counterpart to
the Pure Water.

Shrine maidens performed rituals to prevent it
from overflowing into our world.{end}

#### 195 ####
About Black Water{end}

#### 196 ####
Tainted{end}

#### 197 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}If one is drenched in Black Water, the water of
death, it will slowly consume a person's body.
It will bring them closer to the Netherworld
even as they're still alive. The Black Water taints
the soul, eventually turning it into a ghost.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Only the sacred flame can clean off the
Black Water. This special fire had been carefully
maintained on Mt. Hikami. Those who die from
being tainted by the Black Water become ghosts,
with Black Water pouring out of their mouths
and eyes. They drag the living into the dark.{end}

#### 198 ####
About being tainted{end}

#### 199 ####
Boat of Passage{end}

#### 200 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A boat which took passengers from the Shrine
of the Ephemeral to the Shrine on the Water.
Only shrine maidens who had glanced into
enough people's souls and were suffocated with
grief could board it. It would take them over the
lake without the need to steer.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Should any other person enter the boat, it would
sail into the mist and return to the shore, empty.{end}

#### 201 ####
About the Boat of Passage{end}

#### 202 ####
The Dark Sun{end}

#### 203 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The forever-setting sun that bathes the
Shadowspring, the border between our world
and the Netherworld, in its glow.

It only reveals itself to those who are seeking
death. Its haunting beauty guides them to the
other side.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The souls of the people who follow it to the
Shadowspring resemble shadows, gazing up
into the Dark Sun as they slowly vanish from
our world.{end}

#### 204 ####
About the Dark Sun{end}

#### 205 ####
Ghost Marriage{end}

#### 206 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A posthumous wedding. The tradition of Ghost
Marriage differs from place to place. It was
performed mostly for those who died at a young
age without ever having married, to bring them
happiness in the afterlife.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Participants would be represented by an effigy
or a photograph during the ceremony in which
their soul is wed to a living groom or bride. On
Mt. Hikami, the weddings took place between
sacrificed shrine maidens and Outsiders
brought to the mountain.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The practice was carried out in order to
strengthen the maidens drowned in the
Shadowspring as Pillars; they were believed
to last longer when joined in the darkness
by a partner.

The grooms were free to choose which shrine
maiden they wanted to marry.
{0E:3:0:2:1}If the wedding was successful, the bride would
take the man back with her to the casket in
which she had been drowned. In the event the
wedding did not go as planned, the groom
would be shut in a reliquary and placed in the
water.{end}

#### 207 ####
About Ghost Marriages{end}

#### 208 ####
Immortal Flowers{end}

#### 209 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}This term refers to the shrine maidens drowned
in the Shadowspring as sacrifices. The maidens
were shut in boxes filled with Black Water. The
water brought them close to death and gradually
eroded their bodies. But if their resolve was
strong they would retain their physical form.
{0E:3:0:2:1}While in the caskets, being suspended between
life and death, the shrine maidens would not age.
Their beauty being immune to the effects of time
inspired people to call them Immortal Flowers.{end}

#### 210 ####
About Immortal Flowers{end}

#### 211 ####
Shadowborn{end}

#### 212 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A child born from a union between a living
person and a ghost. Tales of such children are
rare but can be found in many parts of the
world.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Shadowborn were generally feared and detested
as being of the Netherworld, but in some parts
people revere them for their strong psychic
abilities.{end}

#### 213 ####
About the Shadowborn{end}

#### 214 ####
Reliquaries{end}

#### 215 ####
The reliquaries were ornate wooden boxes used
on Mt. Hikami for ritual sacrifices. Shrine
maidens would be shut in the reliquaries, which
would then be placed into the waters.

The ritual was believed to preserve the beauty of
the Pure Water and prevent the Black Water
from tainting it.{end}

#### 216 ####
About the reliquaries{end}

#### 217 ####
Caskets{end}

#### 218 ####
Ornate caskets that were used for ritual
sacrifices. Only the most powerful shrine
maidens were put in these caskets. The caskets
were bigger than the reliquaries so that the
grooms from the Ghost Marriages could join the
shrine maidens in them for eternity, keeping
the Pillars strong.{end}

#### 219 ####
About caskets{end}

#### 220 ####
Shrine Maidens - 2{end}

#### 221 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Shrine maidens were central to the Mt. Hikami
faith. They would accompany people who came
to the mountain to end their life, and be
witnesses to their last moments. Pilgrims would
choose a maiden before entering the mountain.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The maidens would absorb their feelings and
thoughts. After a time, the maidens' hearts
would overflow with these emotions. They
would take that pain with them into the
caskets and reliquaries, which would then be
sunk into the water.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Long ago a man called Kyozo Kururugi killed
the shrine maidens and their bodies washed up
into the Pool of Purification, tainting it with
their blood. This resulted in them becoming
beings of the Netherworld.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They continued to ensure those who come to
Mt. Hikami die a proper death. A few of the
maidens survived and left the mountain. It is
said that they settled in the villages at the foot
of Mt. Hikami and that their abilities live on in
their descendants.{end}

#### 222 ####
About the shrine maidens - 2{end}

#### 223 ####
Glance - 2{end}

#### 224 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A special ability that the shrine maidens
possessed. They would glance into the souls of
people who came to end their life on
Mt. Hikami during their last moments and see
their sins, all their secrets, making those
memories their own.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They would share in those people's sorrow, fears,
and suffering, saving them from the choking
desolation as they died.{end}

#### 225 ####
About the Glance ability - 2{end}

#### 226 ####
{end}

#### 227 ####
Prologue{end}

#### 228 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu, a girl who has been "spirited away," awakes
in a flooded mansion. While searching for the
exit, she comes across a room with nothing but a
large, black box inside.

As the box opens, what emerges from within is
not of this world.
{0E:3:0:2:1}With no one there to hear Miu's scream, her
voice is lost in the mist.{end}

#### 229 ####
Prologue - Lurking in the Depths -{end}

#### 230 ####
First Drop{end}

#### 231 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}While learning about shadow reading from
Hisoka, Yuri uses the ability to retrieve an album
of Postmortem Photographs from a ruined inn
on Mt. Hikami. The album has been requested
by a certain Ren Hojo.
{0E:3:0:2:1}As Ren awakes from a bad dream, he finds
himself tormented by uncertainty.

Was it really just a dream? Or a suppressed
childhood memory? This question has plagued
him for some time.{end}

#### 232 ####
First Drop - A Vanishing Trace -{end}

#### 233 ####
Second Drop{end}

#### 234 ####
Fuyuhi Himino takes her own life. Yuri
witnesses her final moments. Fuyuhi isn't alone
when she dies. There is a woman there who
killed herself in the same way, and a shrine
maiden, sodden from the rain.

Yuri finds Hisoka's Camera Obscura and a charm
Hisoka always liked to wear. She has no choice
but to return to the antiques shop alone.{end}

#### 235 ####
Second Drop - Mt. Hikami -{end}

#### 236 ####
Third Drop{end}

#### 237 ####
The photo album left by the innkeeper was put
together by a folklorist who lived on
Mt. Hikami.

As Ren and Rui explore the inn and follow the
trace of its owner, a ghost lures Rui to suicide.
Then, in the rain, a shrine maiden appears.

Ren and Rui leave the mountain with more
questions than when they started.{end}

#### 238 ####
Third Drop - Postmortem Photography -{end}

#### 239 ####
Interlude{end}

#### 240 ####
Using the Camera Obscura, Yuri finds many
more missing person cases in Hisoka's files. She
is more determined than ever now to head back
to the mountain and find Hisoka.{end}

#### 241 ####
Interlude - Shadow Reading -{end}

#### 242 ####
Fourth Drop{end}

#### 243 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri finds the missing Haruka Momose in a
reliquary in a cave beneath the Shrine of Dolls.

She takes the girl back to the shop. Haruka is in
no state to talk and can't explain what happened
to her.
{0E:3:0:2:1}That night, Haruka is visited by Fuyuhi's ghost,
which takes her back to the mountain.{end}

#### 244 ####
Fourth Drop - Spirited Away -{end}

#### 245 ####
Fifth Drop{end}

#### 246 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren and Rui set out to find the folklorist's
house, relying on clues from a video.

As they pass through the Shrine of Dolls, the
white-haired girl from Ren's dreams appears. She
asks why he didn't bring her token, then
vanishes.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren and Rui arrive at the Veiled House, where
they discover several of Keiji Watarai's writings
on the customs and beliefs surrounding
Mt. Hikami.

They escape the house, only to see it vanish in a
veil of mist.{end}

#### 247 ####
Fifth Drop - The Veiled House -{end}

#### 248 ####
Sixth Drop{end}

#### 249 ####
Miu Hinasaki is found in a reliquary within
the Shrine of the Ephemeral. Yuri attempts to
glance the sleeping Miu's memories, but finds
the tables turned against her.

It seems Miu possesses the same shadow reading
abilities as Yuri.{end}

#### 250 ####
Sixth Drop - Immortal Flower -{end}

#### 251 ####
Seventh Drop{end}

#### 252 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri follows Hisoka's trace to the shore of the
Lake of the Departed, where it vanishes into the
mist. In her place, a woman appears: the same
dark presence seen in Hisoka's photograph.

Unable to inflict any damage with the Camera
Obscura, Yuri's only option is to run.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri recalls the outline of a large torii gate over
the misty lake. Could that be where Hisoka was
headed?{end}

#### 253 ####
Seventh Drop - Maiden of Black Water -{end}

#### 254 ####
Eighth Drop{end}

#### 255 ####
Ren is watching over the sleeping Yuri and Miu
on the surveillance cameras, but he passes out.
He has a dream where he's chasing after Rui.
When he wakes up, both Yuri and Rui are gone.

He finds Miu getting ready to leave for
Mt. Hikami, taking Yuri's Camera Obscura with
her. She heads for the door, leaving a
bewildered Ren behind.{end}

#### 256 ####
Eighth Drop - The Witching Hour -{end}

#### 257 ####
Ninth Drop{end}

#### 258 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}As Yuri wades into the mist over the Lake of the
Departed, she is stopped by Miu.

The girls grow closer. Losing their parents at a
young age and being able to see into the souls of
others... The girls have more in common than
they may have first realized.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri still hasn't found Hisoka, while Miu still
searches for her mother, Miku.

The eerie dark figure that appeared at the lake
may just hold all the answers. But why does she
keep calling out to Yuri?{end}

#### 259 ####
Ninth Drop - The Sacred Casket -{end}

#### 260 ####
Tenth Drop{end}

#### 261 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren finds Rui in the Veiled House, only to be
pulled into a reliquary. He awakes in an
unfamiliar building.

An old woman leads Ren to a room in which
Rui is waiting, dressed as a bride. The room
where the Ghost Marriages are held.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui changes into a fearsome bride wearing black.
Then, in a flash, they are back in the folklorist's
house. There they encounter Kazuya, whose own
wedding to a ghost went horribly wrong.

The Veiled House vanishes, with Kazuya still
inside.{end}

#### 262 ####
Tenth Drop - Ghost Marriage -{end}

#### 263 ####
Eleventh Drop{end}

#### 264 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu finally finds Miku on Mt. Hikami, where
she had entered into a Ghost Marriage at the
House of Joining.

Miku explains her desire to be reunited with her
beloved, pleading for forgiveness. 

They head back to the shop.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu and Miku lay side by side and quickly fall
into a deep sleep.{end}

#### 265 ####
Eleventh Drop - The Shadowborn -{end}

#### 266 ####
Twelfth Drop{end}

#### 267 ####
Yuri boards the Boat of Passage and is taken to
the Shrine on the Water, the final destination for
shrine maidens set to become Pillars.

Yuri finds Hisoka inside the shrine and takes her
safely back to the antiques shop.

The bond between the two of them grows even
stronger.{end}

#### 268 ####
Twelfth Drop - To the Other Side -{end}

#### 269 ####
Thirteenth Drop{end}

#### 270 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren learns of the true purpose of the rituals
performed on Mt. Hikami.

The mountain acts as a bridge between our
world and the world of the dead. A place at
which the souls of visitors are returned to the
water from which they were born.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Shrine maidens absorbed the memories of the
dying, and when they could take no more, they
were sacrificed.

Ghost Marriages served to strengthen the souls
of those sacrificed.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They sunk deep into that spring of darkness that
leads to the Netherworld.

The water is everything.{end}

#### 271 ####
Thirteenth Drop - The Dark Sun -{end}

#### 272 ####
Bride from Black Water{end}

#### 273 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Having absorbed the thoughts of countless
ghosts, Yuri feels the mountain calling for her.
She makes her way toward the Shadowspring.

Awaiting her is Ose Kurosawa, the Immortal
Flower. As Yuri touches Ose, she shares in her
immense pain and solitude.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ose, finally freed from her grief, returns to the
Shadowspring alone.

Entering her casket, she takes with her
all the Black Water which had spilled out onto
the mountain, to eternally fall into its depths.

Yuri leaves the mountain with Hisoka.{end}

#### 274 ####
Last Drop - Bride from Black Water -{end}

#### 275 ####
Embrace{end}

#### 276 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Having absorbed the thoughts of countless
ghosts, Yuri feels the mountain calling for her.
She makes her way toward the Shadowspring.

Awaiting her is Ose Kurosawa, the Immortal
Flower. Yuri and Ose share the same pain, grief
and isolation. They fall as one.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They are no longer alone.{end}

#### 277 ####
Last Drop - Embrace -{end}

#### 278 ####
Love After Death{end}

#### 279 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren roams Mt. Hikami, following Dr. Aso's
memories. The trail leads him to his own
Ghost Marriage.

The bride Ren has chosen is waiting for him in
the House of Joining. It's the bride from the
photo, Ose Kurosawa.
{0E:3:0:2:1}As Ren embraces Ose, the scene changes and
now it's Dr. Aso standing there with Ose.
Kunihiko tells Ose how he feels. She disappears,
happy.

She returns to the darkness to continue serving
as a Pillar. Ren is allowed to leave the mountain.{end}

#### 280 ####
Last Drop - Love after Death -{end}

#### 281 ####
Alone in the Casket{end}

#### 282 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren roams Mt. Hikami, following Dr. Aso's
memories. The trail leads him to his own
Ghost Marriage.

The bride Ren has chosen is waiting for him in
the House of Joining. It's the bride from the
photo, Ose Kurosawa.
{0E:3:0:2:1}As she approaches, Ren takes a picture of her,
stopping her from getting close. She accepts his
rejection and asks that he take one last picture.

Ren grants her that wish and she disappears, to
return to her duties as a Pillar, leaving Ren the
picture, and her soul.{end}

#### 283 ####
Last Drop - Alone in the Casket -{end}

#### 284 ####
In the Reliquary{end}

#### 285 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren roams Mt. Hikami, following Dr. Aso's
memories. The trail leads him to his own
Ghost Marriage.

The bride Ren has chosen is waiting for him in
the House of Joining. It's the white-haired girl,
Shiragiku.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They enter her reliquary, where Ren turns into a
young Dr. Aso. In this way, the vow he made to
her is fulfilled. Now, Shiragiku remembers the
first time they met, and pushes him away,
choosing to remain alone as a Pillar.

Ren wakes up outside Kagiroi Shrine, where
Dr. Aso used to play with Shiragiku when they
were children.{end}

#### 286 ####
Last Drop - In the Reliquary -{end}

#### 287 ####
Cherry Blossoms{end}

#### 288 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren roams Mt. Hikami, following Dr. Aso's
memories. The trail leads him to his own
Ghost Marriage.

The bride Ren has chosen is waiting for him in
the House of Joining. It's the white-haired girl,
Shiragiku.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren is scared of her reliquary, and defeats her
with his Camera Obscura. She is thus relieved of
her duties as a Pillar, and forgives both Ren and
Dr. Aso. She recalls a memory of beautiful
cherry blossoms, thinking of them as she fades
away.{end}

#### 289 ####
Last Drop - Cherry Blossoms -{end}

#### 290 ####
The Shadowborn{end}

#### 291 ####
Miu and her mother watch the Dark Sun as it
sinks into the Black Water. Miku promises never
to leave Miu again.

It's a lie.

A lie that hurts more than the truth. Miu knows
that her mother is no longer of this world. Her
mother vanishes and Miu, now alone, cries out.{end}

#### 292 ####
Last Drop - The Shadowborn -{end}

#### 293 ####
Waking up to Dreams{end}

#### 294 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu and her mother watch the Dark Sun as it
sinks into the Black Water. Miku promises never
to leave Miu again.

Miu wakes up. Her mother is there next to her.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They embrace, each making sure the other is
really there. Even if it's just for a while...{end}

#### 295 ####
Last Drop - Waking up to Dreams -{end}

#### 296 ####
First Thread{end}

#### 297 ####
Ayane agrees to look for a missing girl called
Tsumugi. She learns she is on Mt. Hikami, and
is severely wounded by a ghost.

She makes her escape and decides the only way
to fight the supernatural is with forbidden
magic.{end}

#### 298 ####
First Thread - Stranger in the Rain -{end}

#### 299 ####
Second Thread{end}

#### 300 ####
Ayane casts a spell on herself bringing her closer
to death. Shrouded in darkness, she follows the
purple thread leading her to Tsumugi.

The thread leads her to the Shrine of the
Ephemeral, on the summit of Mt. Hikami.{end}

#### 301 ####
Second Thread - Purple Ties -{end}

#### 302 ####
Third Thread{end}

#### 303 ####
Ayane searches the Shrine of the Ephemeral.

She finds and rescues Tsumugi, who was being
swallowed by the Black Water.

She can feel that they are surrounded by beings
from the Netherworld.{end}

#### 304 ####
Third Thread - Shrine of the Ephemeral -{end}

#### 305 ####
Last Thread{end}

#### 306 ####
Ayane and Tsumugi escape from Mt. Hikami.

She has something to say to the girl. She tells
her to believe in herself.

As Ayane turns to leave, Tsumugi replies that
she will become stronger.{end}

#### 307 ####
Last Thread - Wash Away -{end}

