#### 1 ####
Yuri: Twilit Cliff{end}

#### 2 ####
Yuri's memory. Standing on a cliff in the evening sun,
she contemplates stepping over the edge.{end}

#### 3 ####
Ren: Ceremony Dream{end}

#### 4 ####
Ren Hojo's dream. He's a boy, and at a ceremony.
It's night. He stabs a girl... Did it really happen?{end}

#### 5 ####
Fuyuhi: Shared Promise{end}

#### 6 ####
Fuyuhi's memory. She and Haruka are the only ones left.
They make a promise to each other.{end}

#### 7 ####
Hisoka: Misty Lake{end}

#### 8 ####
Hisoka stands in a lake. A woman emerges from
her reflection and pulls her under the surface.{end}

#### 9 ####
Fuyuhi: Final Moments{end}

#### 10 ####
Fuyuhi's final living moment. The last things she
sees as she raises a blade to her throat.{end}

#### 11 ####
Haruka: Lured by Dusk{end}

#### 12 ####
Haruka follows the setting sun. She sees the glow of a mirror,
then ends up trapped in a reliquary.{end}

#### 13 ####
Ren: Girl Glances Back{end}

#### 14 ####
Ren's dream. As he holds a blade, the girl in front
of him slowly turns around, filling him with fear.{end}

#### 15 ####
Miu: Dragged Under{end}

#### 16 ####
Miu's memory. As she investigates an old house,
countless ghostly arms pull her under the water.{end}

#### 17 ####
Miu: Lies and Fear{end}

#### 18 ####
Miu's memories of a photo shoot.
Cut to Yuri's memories of a lurking, deathly shadow.{end}

#### 19 ####
Miu: Boat of Passage{end}

#### 20 ####
Miu dreams she's on a boat in the fog.
Another boat drifts by, carrying a bride. It's her mother.{end}

#### 21 ####
Yuri: Hisoka on a Cliff{end}

#### 22 ####
Yuri's memory. Hisoka stands at a cliff's edge
in the evening sun. Yuri stops her from jumping.{end}

#### 23 ####
Yuri: Warm Coffee{end}

#### 24 ####
Yuri's memory. After being saved by Hisoka,
she takes comfort from a warm cup of coffee.{end}

#### 25 ####
Miku: Ghost Marriage{end}

#### 26 ####
Miku's memory. Beckoned by the setting sun,
she takes part in a ceremony of Ghost Marriage.{end}

#### 27 ####
Yuri: Death All Around{end}

#### 28 ####
Yuri's memory. She can't escape the stench of death.
It's all around her, but only she can sense it.{end}

#### 29 ####
Dr. Aso: Two Tokens{end}

#### 30 ####
Kunihiko Aso's memory. A lady in white and a girl
with white hair. They each give him tokens.{end}

#### 31 ####
Shiragiku: Into a Box{end}

#### 32 ####
Shiragiku's memory. She hides in her secret place
with a young Kunihiko when they first meet.{end}

#### 33 ####
Dr. Aso: Undying Love{end}

#### 34 ####
Kunihiko Aso's memory. His final rendezvous.
He thought he'd never see her again.{end}

#### 35 ####
Ose: Pain and Darkness{end}

#### 36 ####
Ose Kurosawa's memory. What she saw as an
Immortal Flower. Her pain and sorrow.{end}

#### 37 ####
Ose: Embrace{end}

#### 38 ####
Ose Kurosawa's memory. She embraces the pain
and descends eternally into the darkness, alone.{end}

#### 39 ####
Hisoka: Here and Gone{end}

#### 40 ####
Hisoka's memory. A girl jumps to her death.
Her last words haunt Hisoka to this day.{end}

#### 41 ####
Rui: Face in the Mirror{end}

#### 42 ####
Rui's memory. She ponders her feelings for Ren
and the ambiguity of their relationship.{end}

#### 43 ####
Funeral Celebrant{end}

#### 44 ####
The Funeral Celebrant's memory. The ritual fails
and Black Water overflows. Darkness descends.{end}

#### 45 ####
Pale Mistress{end}

#### 46 ####
A Pale Mistress is shut in a reliquary and thrown
into the Shadowspring. There she waits alone.{end}

#### 47 ####
Twisted Guardian{end}

#### 48 ####
A sacrificed maiden is shut into a reliquary and
thrown into the Shadowspring as a Pillar.{end}

#### 49 ####
Guardian{end}

#### 50 ####
Black Water spills over from the Shadowspring.
It consumes everything, and everyone, in its path.{end}

#### 51 ####
Flamekeeper{end}

#### 52 ####
While the Flamekeepers watch over the Forbidden Flame,
one man's actions bring about grave calamity.{end}

#### 53 ####
Shadow-touched{end}

#### 54 ####
Men carrying reliquaries to the Shadowspring
are consumed by the Black Water upon touching it.{end}

#### 55 ####
Black Water Maiden 2{end}

#### 56 ####
A Maiden of Black Water takes on the final thoughts
of the dying, then returns to the water.{end}

#### 57 ####
Black Water Maiden 1{end}

#### 58 ####
The fate of all who come to the mountain,
once glanced by a Maiden of Black Water.{end}

#### 59 ####
Blood-soaked Maidens{end}

#### 60 ####
A group of shrine maidens are brutally murdered.
Their eyes are pulverized, but one maiden sees all.{end}

#### 61 ####
Shino Kururugi{end}

#### 62 ####
A shrine maiden glances into a woman's soul.
As if under a spell, she hangs herself.{end}

#### 63 ####
Kirika Reizen{end}

#### 64 ####
A woman slits her throat under the gaze of a Maiden of Black Water.{end}

#### 65 ####
Hiori Magabuchi{end}

#### 66 ####
As a woman plummets to her death, a Maiden of
Black Water watches on from the clifftop above.{end}

#### 67 ####
Tomoki Harakawa{end}

#### 68 ####
A man contemplates hanging himself. As he
hesitates and looks down, he loses his footing.{end}

#### 69 ####
Yukiho Tomine{end}

#### 70 ####
A woman sees something she shouldn't have and
finds herself pushed toward the same fate.{end}

#### 71 ####
Hiromichi Kashima{end}

#### 72 ####
On a routine drive through Mt. Hikami,
a man ends up being run over by his own car.{end}

#### 73 ####
Watarai: Bride in Black{end}

#### 74 ####
Keiji Watarai's memory. He arrives at the House
of Joining, where a bride wearing black awaits.{end}

#### 75 ####
Kazuya: A Painful End{end}

#### 76 ####
Kazuya's failed Ghost Marriage. After having
second thoughts, his bride inflicts a brutal death.{end}

#### 77 ####
Shiragiku: Blossoms{end}

#### 78 ####
Shiragiku's memory. Before her life ended, she
wanted to witness something beautiful.{end}

#### 79 ####
Kyozo Kururugi{end}

#### 80 ####
Kyozo's secrets and sins had been seen. He kills
all the maidens, then takes his own life.{end}

#### 81 ####
People from the Water{end}

#### 82 ####
As people die, they merge with the water. The
more people die, the more they blend together.{end}

#### 83 ####
Chased Man{end}

#### 84 ####
A man's final moments caught on video. By the
time he turns around, it's already too late.{end}

#### 85 ####
Video: Lost Woman{end}

#### 86 ####
A video recording of the Veiled House. A woman
finds more inside than she bargained for...{end}

#### 87 ####
The Children{end}

#### 88 ####
The sobbing of children is heard at twilight.
They disappear into the mist, never to return.{end}

#### 89 ####
Woman with Umbrella{end}

#### 90 ####
On a rainy day, the descendant of a shrine maiden
consoles the souls of those lost to the mountain.{end}

#### 91 ####
To be continued...{end}

#### 92 ####
After Fuyuhi disappears, a lone shrine maiden appears before Yuri.{end}

#### 93 ####
Previously...{end}

#### 94 ####
Following the trace of a missing person, Yuri loses her way on Mt. Hikami.{end}

#### 95 ####
Miu: The Dark Sun{end}

#### 96 ####
The sun sets over the Lake of the Departed. As Miu stares at the beautiful
scene, her mother disappears, and she begins to cry.{end}

