#### 1 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I must have passed out.
This mist isn't a good sign.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Is Rui OK?{end}

#### 2 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I can't stop thinking about what Rui said.


{0E:3:0:2:1}What I'm looking for is in my study?


{0E:3:0:2:1}What does it mean?{end}

#### 3 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I found this photo in my family's storeroom,
together with the Camera Obscura.
It belonged to the man I saw in my dream, Dr. Aso.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I can use it to follow his trace.
It may finally shed some light on Mt. Hikami's past.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I want to know what he was doing there.
And how to put an end to all this.{end}

#### 4 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The Camera Obscura was in this box when I found it.

{0E:3:0:2:1}This must mean it belonged to Dr. Aso.
{0E:3:0:2:1}It looks like there's something else inside.{end}

#### 5 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}If this was left behind by Dr. Aso,
then the dream of the ritual...was a memory of his?
{0E:3:0:2:1}That girl, she's waiting for the person she gave this lock of her hair to...
For Dr. Aso.
{0E:3:0:2:1}What did he see on Mt. Hikami?
And how is it related to the current events?

{0E:3:0:2:1}This photograph and the lock of hair might lead to the answers I seek.{end}

#### 6 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri's gone.


{0E:3:0:2:1}Has she been taken back to the mountain again?{end}

#### 7 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I had that box the camera was in when I found it...


{0E:3:0:2:1}It belonged to Dr. Aso.
I should check if it doesn't hold any other useful items.

{0E:3:0:2:1}I put it away somewhere in this room.{end}

#### 8 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}What did Dr. Aso do?
What can I do? What should I do?

{0E:3:0:2:1}I need to see for myself.{end}

#### 9 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Is this Dr. Aso?


{0E:3:0:2:1}The only person who left Mt. Hikami alive.
But what was he doing here? What did he take pictures of?

{0E:3:0:2:1}If I try photographing what he's looking at, I may just find some clues.{end}

#### 10 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The path leading up the mountain.


{0E:3:0:2:1}This place used to be called Maiden Grove.
This is where pilgrims chose the shrine maiden to accompany them.
{0E:3:0:2:1}A shrine maiden...who would oversee their demise.{end}

#### 11 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}This is the Pool of Purification.


{0E:3:0:2:1}Pilgrims would undergo a rite of purification here.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Soaking in these waters would make them one with the mountain
and bring them closer to the world of the dead.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The shrine maidens always kept their raven-black hair soaked.
They were known as Maidens of Black Water...{end}

#### 12 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The girl with white hair.

{0E:3:0:2:1}She gave a token to Dr. Aso when he was a boy
and later came to this mountain.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Then she waited for him to come back to her, guided by the token.{end}

#### 13 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The Forbidden Valley.


{0E:3:0:2:1}Outsiders who participated in Ghost Marriages were buried here.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Whether the ceremony was a success or not, they were all interred.{end}

#### 14 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}In time, Mt. Hikami became known as a haunted place
where people come to commit suicide. It seemed to attract death.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Many young girls who disappeared ended up here,
and probably stayed here as Pillars...{end}

#### 15 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Mt. Hikami is a mountain of death.
A place people are drawn to when they want to die.
{0E:3:0:2:1}What did those shrine maidens mean to the people who came here to die?

{0E:3:0:2:1}What did the grooms see in their long-dead brides?

{0E:3:0:2:1}And Dr. Aso, what did he think of it all?

{0E:3:0:2:1}The things he wanted to see...he wanted to do...
The places he wanted to visit. The people he wanted to meet...{end}

