#### 1 ####
That should do it.{end}

#### 2 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui seems to be unconscious...
Or maybe just asleep.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I wonder what that rumbling was.
Something must be happening on the mountain.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri and Miu have both been affected by the noise.
I should make sure that they're OK.{end}

#### 3 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui is still asleep.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I hope Yuri and Miu are all right.
I should check the surveillance camera feed.{end}

#### 4 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Something strange is happening.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Patrolling the hallways won't do much good.
It'd be easier to check the surveillance cameras.{end}

#### 5 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Haruka Momose, the girl Yuri saved, was led away
by the ghost of a girl who killed herself.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Something might have come again.
I need to check the surveillance camera feeds to see if the girls are OK.{end}

#### 6 ####
Let's see if there are any books in this room about Mt. Hikami.{end}

#### 7 ####
I really need to investigate Mt. Hikami and find out
what's going on there.{end}

#### 8 ####
I have to check if Yuri and Miu are OK.{end}

#### 9 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}They both seem to be fine. But I should keep
checking on them every now and then, just to be sure.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They've been acting strange since that ominous rumble.
What's happening on Mt. Hikami?
{0E:3:0:2:1}I should look into the mountain's history.
They must have some books about it here.{end}

#### 10 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Press {0E:4:0:2:1CD}{0E:0:1:2:1}{E008}{0E:4:0:2:CD}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF} to stop watching the feed and get up.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:0:1:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}{0E:0:1:2:FFFF}If something strange happens on the camera,
get up and investigate it.{end}

#### 11 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}There's static in the feed from Yuri's room.
I'd better go and check it out.{end}

#### 12 ####
Is she all right?{end}

#### 13 ####
She seems to be having a nightmare, but is otherwise OK.{end}

#### 14 ####
I should get back to watching the surveillance camera feed.{end}

#### 15 ####
There's static in the feed from Miu's room.
I'd better go and check it out.{end}

#### 16 ####
Everything seems normal.
Maybe it was just static.{end}

#### 17 ####
I should go and check on Miu, just in case.{end}

#### 18 ####
Why is the TV on?{end}

#### 19 ####
There's nothing but static on the screen.{end}

#### 20 ####
I should probably switch the TV off.{end}

#### 21 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The camera in Yuri's room is off.
What's going on?
{0E:3:0:2:1}I should go check it out.{end}

#### 22 ####
Wait, where...? Rui must have woken up...{end}

#### 23 ####
The camera in Yuri's room is off.
Something might be happening in there...{end}

#### 24 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I've got to stay in here and keep checking the camera feeds
to make sure the girls are OK.{end}

