#### 1 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}That light...
{0E:3:0:2:1}It might be a sign of something strange happening on Mt. Hikami.
Something might be on its way here again.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I should keep an eye on the surveillance camera feeds.{end}

#### 2 ####
{end}

#### 3 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The door is being held shut by a powerful force.
It's probably the owner of that black hair I saw out of the window.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I have to watch over the girls.
Checking the camera feeds is more efficient than patrolling.{end}

#### 4 ####
I've got to make sure the girls are safe here.
Besides, I can't get out...{end}

#### 5 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}That's the room Miu and her mother are sleeping in.
I've got to rescue them...{end}

#### 6 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I can't go in there with the ghost still chasing me.{end}

#### 7 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I've got to lose this ghost first.{end}

#### 8 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui is breathing quietly, in deep slumber.
What's that book?
{0E:3:0:2:1}It's about folk tales surrounding Mt. Hikami.
I should probably take a look at it as well.{end}

#### 9 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I might as well read the book Rui found.
It may be helpful.{end}

#### 10 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui is all right.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The spirits aren't here yet.
I should go check on Miu and her mother.{end}

#### 11 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}It won't open...
{0E:3:0:2:1}I should check the camera feed.{end}

#### 12 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui's having nightmares, but seems OK otherwise.{end}

#### 13 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui's not waking up...
{0E:3:0:2:1}I'm a bit worried, but for now I need to stay here
and keep checking on everyone.{end}

#### 14 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Hisoka...
She looks like she's having a nightmare, but otherwise seems fine.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She spent days trapped on Mt. Hikami.
I'd like to ask her about what she saw there...
{0E:3:0:2:1}...But I've got more urgent things on my hands right now.
I should keep watching the camera feeds.{end}

#### 15 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}No ghosts in sight.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I can't let my guard down though.
I need to keep checking on everyone.{end}

#### 16 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri is bathed in the red glow, but is still in a deep sleep.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Everything seems to be fine in her room.{end}

#### 17 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Something has fallen under the bed.
{0E:3:0:2:1}A book Yuri was reading? It might be worth checking out.{end}

#### 18 ####
I need to check if she's OK...{end}

#### 19 ####
I should check what that book under Yuri's bed is about.
It may have some information about Mt. Hikami.{end}

#### 20 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}It doesn't look like Yuri will wake up any time soon.
It's got to be the influence of this disturbing light.{end}

#### 21 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri ventured all over Mt. Hikami looking for Hisoka,
and the others before that. She may have been affected by it.
I need to be careful.{end}

#### 22 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri seems fine for now.
Her room is ghost-free, but they might still come.
I'll keep watch over her from the office.{end}

#### 23 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The two Hinasakis are sleeping together.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They deserve a rest. I have to watch over everyone though, not just them.{end}

#### 24 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miku Hinasaki... She looks so young,
you could mistake her for Miu's sister.
{0E:3:0:2:1}She's been on Mt. Hikami for years,
trapped on the border between the worlds of the living and the dead.
{0E:3:0:2:1}In a place where time stands still.{end}

#### 25 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}They seem to be all right. Except for the nightmares...
{0E:3:0:2:1}The ghost I saw walk in is nowhere to be seen.{end}

#### 26 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Something's definitely coming this way from the mountain.
{0E:3:0:2:1}It's too dangerous to just walk around.
I should return to the office and watch the surveillance feed.{end}

#### 27 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I saw a ghost entering this room...
{0E:3:0:2:1}Are the Hinasakis okay?{end}

#### 28 ####
The ghost is gone for now, but I should check out her room just in case.{end}

#### 29 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Inhabitants of Mt. Hikami have long held peculiar beliefs
about life and death.
{0E:3:0:2:1}People would go there for special rituals and offer their lives
to the dark waters of the mountain lake.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Mt. Hikami has always been known for the many suicides
that take place there.{end}

#### 30 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The religion practiced on Mt. Hikami relied on the shrine maidens.
They were the ones guarding the border between worlds.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They had two main duties. The first one was to oversee
the deaths of those who made the pilgrimage to Mt. Hikami.
{0E:3:0:2:1}And the second one...{end}

#### 31 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I've been here before. This is where the Ghost Marriage
ceremonies were held.{end}

#### 32 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The door is being held shut by a powerful force.{end}

#### 33 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I'm worried about what's going on in the other rooms.
I should check the camera feed.{end}

