#### 1 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:2:0:2:4ACD}Haruka Momose...
This is the girl that Fuyuhi was looking for.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Hisoka must have been trying to find her.{end}

#### 2 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The door is being held shut by a powerful force.
Haruka is inside. There must be another way in.{end}

#### 3 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The door is being held shut by a powerful force.{end}

#### 4 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The door is being held shut by a powerful force.{end}

#### 5 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}There are stairs below the doll display.
Haruka might have gone down there.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The wooden grate won't budge.
There must be a way to open it.{end}

#### 6 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}This wooden grate won't budge.
There must be a way to open it.{end}

#### 7 ####
This photo might be showing me where to find the hidden effigy.{end}

#### 8 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I found this {0E:1:0:2:9CD}Effigy{0E:1:2:0} on the floor.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I should put it back on the doll display.{end}

#### 9 ####
I should probably stay here for now.{end}

#### 10 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I just spoke with Mr. Hojo.
He agreed that we should come by as often as we can
until Ms. Kurosawa gets back.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Having someone be there for you can be a huge
comfort at times like this.{end}

#### 11 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}We'll do all we can to help you find Ms. Kurosawa.
Don't hesitate to ask us if you need anything.
{0E:3:0:2:3}I'm certain Ms. Kurosawa will be fine.
She's a very strong, resourceful person.
{0E:3:0:2:4}...Unlike Mr. Hojo.{end}

#### 12 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}You say...
Ms. Himino cut her own throat?
{0E:3:0:2:2}Mr. Hojo was telling me...
He said I tried to hang myself on the inn roof.
{0E:3:0:2:3}Thankfully, he was there to save me.
{0E:3:0:2:4}The shrine maiden that appeared after Ms. Himino's suicide
might have been the same one that we saw on the roof.
{0E:3:0:2:5}Something very strange is happening on that mountain.{end}

#### 13 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}If you're looking for Mr. Hojo, he's in the office.
{0E:3:0:2:2}He seemed quite exhausted, so he may be taking a nap.
{0E:3:0:2:3}Has he no shame... Oh, I'm sorry.
Feel free to wake him up if you need him.{end}

#### 14 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}There's no one in Hisoka's room.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I should tell Ren and Rui that she isn't back yet.{end}

#### 15 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}That dream... It was just like the memory I saw
when I touched Haruka in that cave. 
{0E:3:0:2:1}I need to know more. Maybe if I ask her...{end}

#### 16 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The door is locked.
The lock is broken, I won't be able to open it.{end}

#### 17 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The door is locked.
{0E:3:0:2:1}An iris flower is engraved on the lock.
It seems I can't get out this way.{end}

#### 18 ####
He must be having a terrible nightmare.{end}

#### 19 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Haruka's trace led me to this room.
{0E:3:0:2:1}There must be some clues here.{end}

#### 20 ####
There's no sign of Haruka this way.
I need to follow her trace.{end}

#### 21 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Haruka didn't come this way.
Her trace led me inside the building.{end}

#### 22 ####
An old doll appeared in the place shown in the photograph.{end}

#### 23 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I have to follow Haruka's trace.{end}

#### 24 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}I can't shake off these ghosts.
I have to think of something...{end}

#### 25 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:2:0:2:2CCD}You placed the {0E:1:0:2:9CD}Effigy{0E:1:2:0} on the doll display.{end}

#### 26 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}It sounded as if something moved beneath the doll display.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The wooden lattice blocking the hidden staircase has opened.{end}

#### 27 ####
The camera is reacting to something...{end}

#### 28 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The girl was sitting in the middle of the doll display.
I should try placing the doll there.{end}

#### 29 ####
Haruka is somewhere in this shrine...{end}

#### 30 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}There's something in the photo...
{0E:3:0:2:1}It looks like a person...hanging from a tree.{end}

#### 31 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Was that...Haruka?
{0E:3:0:2:1}Is there something under the doll display?{end}

#### 32 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}A richly decorated black box is submerged in the water.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The lid is shut...{end}

#### 33 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}It's another black box like the one Haruka was in, it's underwater.
{0E:3:0:2:1}The lid is shut.
Is someone inside this one, too?{end}

#### 34 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The box the ghost came out of is open.
It's full of dark water.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Something that looks disturbingly like hair is floating on the surface.{end}

#### 35 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Haruka...
I'd better give her some time to recover.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I have to tell Ren and Rui about Hisoka...{end}

#### 36 ####
It sounded like something fell into the bushes.{end}

#### 37 ####
There's a doll on the stairs.{end}

#### 38 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Haruka...
I'd better give her some time to recover.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I have to tell Ren and Rui about Hisoka...{end}

#### 39 ####
I found Haruka.
We need to get off this mountain.{end}

