#### 1 ####
The sliding door is being held shut by some powerful force.{end}

#### 2 ####
Ren touches Ose (chooses her)
Ren opens the door to the Ghost Marriage room (chooses Shiragiku){end}

#### 3 ####
Select Token{end}

#### 4 ####
Photo of a Bride{end}

#### 5 ####
Bundle of White Hair{end}

#### 6 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The place where Ghost Marriages took place.
Is someone waiting for me inside?

{0E:3:0:2:1}No, I have to make the choice.
The groom must bring with him the token of his chosen bride.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:2:0:2:42CD}A photo of a bride, she was one of the shrine maidens.

{0E:3:0:2:1}She was offered to the Black Water as a sacrifice and to this day
exists as an Immortal Flower, awaiting her companion.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:2:0:2:21CD}A lock of white hair belonging to a young girl.
It was among Dr. Aso's belongings.

{0E:3:0:2:1}I've been seeing this girl in my dreams.
She gave this token to Dr. Aso when he was a boy.
{0E:3:0:2:1}They are both waiting. Which one do I choose?{end}

#### 7 ####
It's being held by some powerful force.{end}

#### 8 ####
There is something on the floor in the corner.{end}

#### 9 ####
Something got left behind when the girl disappeared.{end}

