#### 1 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}The Shadow Sigil... A curse that allows
the user to connect with the world of the dead.
{0E:3:0:2:1}It enables the user to sense ghosts
while masking their own presence.{end}

#### 2 ####
I sense something...{end}

#### 3 ####
I feel it. It's different from before.{end}

#### 4 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CCD}Tutorial: Spirit Filament{0E:1:2:0}
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}The Spirit Filament will react to a ghost's presence
and indicate its status.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Blue: Unaware. 
The ghost is completely unaware of Ayane's presence.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Yellow: Searching. 
The ghost has sensed Ayane and is looking for her.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Even when they cannot see Ayane, 
ghosts can hear her if she makes a noise.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Red: Attacking. 
The ghost knows where Ayane is and is ready to attack.{end}

#### 5 ####
If you don't run and avoid making noise, ghosts will not notice you.
However, there is something you need to keep in mind.{end}

#### 6 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CCD}Tutorial: Concealment{0E:1:2:0}
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}The purple gauge to the right of the screen shows the degree of your
concealment. It decreases as you near ghosts that can sense you.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}When it reaches zero, all ghosts can see you. 
The gauge recovers when you move out of the ghosts' detection range.{end}

#### 7 ####
{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Ghosts will notice you when you make noise. To avoid detection,
move away from the ghosts and stand still for a while.{end}

#### 8 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}It seems ghosts can sense the Purple Thread. 
{0E:3:0:2:1}I should reel it back in before they react to it.{end}

#### 9 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Avoiding these guys could be tricky...
I should give this thing a try.{end}

#### 10 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:CCD}Tutorial: Spirit Stone Flashlight{0E:1:2:0}
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}This is the only means by which Ayane can fight ghosts.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Flash the flashlight at ghosts multiple times to temporarily stun them.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}You can also charge up the flashlight to stun ghosts with just one flash.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Ghosts will recover after a while, 
but they will have lost track of Ayane by then.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Use the Spirit Stone Flashlight wisely
to get past ghosts that are in your way.{end}

#### 11 ####
It's noticed me. That seemed to have some effect,
but I'll need to hit it with something stronger.{end}

#### 12 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}It seems the ghost has been weakened...
This is my chance to get past.{end}

#### 13 ####
{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Your concealment gauge will not recover while you are running.
To let it recover, move away from ghosts and stand still for a while.{end}

#### 14 ####
This one looks like trouble...{end}

#### 15 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}It's a ghost, but it reeks of blood...
{0E:3:0:2:1}That must be the blood of its victims.
It may have been human once,
but I doubt there's any humanity left now.
{0E:3:0:2:1}I'd better make sure it doesn't notice me.{end}

#### 16 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Tsumugi, she's...inside...
{0E:3:0:2:1}That was a vision. 
Is this another effect of the Shadow Sigil?
{0E:3:0:2:1}Tsumugi must be trapped and close to death...
That may be true of me as well...{end}

#### 17 ####
{end}

#### 18 ####
The Purple Thread isn't pointing that way. 
I have to stay focused.{end}

#### 19 ####
The thread leads towards that shrine.{end}

#### 20 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Was that Tsumugi?!
{0E:3:0:2:1}N-no, it couldn't have...{end}

#### 21 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}This is where the Purple Thread is telling me to go.
{0E:3:0:2:1}That must have been an illusion... 
Or perhaps it was a vision of the past.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Anyway, the thread will lead me to Tsumugi.
I just have to trust in it.{end}

#### 22 ####
It hasn't noticed me... 
Should I wait for it to go away?{end}

#### 23 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Ghosts will be drawn to any noise you make.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Walking will alert them more than when you stand still,
and running will quickly bring them down upon you.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}The safest option is to stand still and wait
for the spirit to go past, and then walk upstairs.{end}

#### 24 ####
I can sense... There's three of them.{end}

#### 25 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}If ghosts get too close to you, even if you don't move,
your concealment gauge will go down and you'll be spotted.
{0E:3:0:2:1}{0E:1:0:2:ECD}Sometimes you may have to quietly approach a ghost
and stun it with the Spirit Stone Flashlight.{end}

#### 26 ####
I can't sense it anymore. With the flashlight and the Shadow Sigil,
I'll be able to get Tsumugi out of here.{end}

