#### 1 ####
- Spirited Away -

In the vicinity of Mt. Hikami, people have been mysteriously
disappearing without a trace.

One such girl is Miu Hinasaki. She awakens to find herself in an
old, half-flooded building.{end}

#### 2 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}- Shadow Reading -

Among the residents of the villages at the foot of Mt. Hikami,
a certain unique ability has been passed through the ages.

This ability, known as "shadow reading," enables the user
to view the shadow, or "trace," of someone lost in inexplicable
circumstances. This is not unlike the "psychometry" practiced
elsewhere.

Yuri Kozukata accompanies Hisoka Kurosawa, a woman who
possesses the shadow reading ability, to an abandoned inn on
Mt. Hikami.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Sensing Yuri could in time become talented at shadow reading,
Hisoka takes her along on an assignment.{end}

#### 3 ####
A few days have passed since Yuri's introduction to
shadow reading at the abandoned inn.

Since then, Hisoka has gone off somewhere and hasn't returned.
Yuri worries for Hisoka, but isn't sure how or where to start
searching.

As she sits waiting at the antiques shop, a girl named Fuyuhi
Himino shows up, claiming to have enlisted Hisoka to help
her find a missing person.{end}

#### 4 ####
Ren Hojo, a writer, is haunted by a recurring dream in which he
kills a young girl during a ritual.

He receives an album of Postmortem Photographs, located on his
request by Hisoka. Upon viewing one of the photos, Ren
recognizes the very scene from his dreams.

Eager to delve further into this puzzling mystery, Ren heads to
the abandoned inn in person this time, bringing along his
assistant, Rui Kagamiya.{end}

#### 5 ####
With Hisoka still missing, Yuri recalls what she witnessed on the
mountain: Fuyuhi, taking her own life while entranced by a
malevolent spirit, and the bodies of dead shrine maidens washed
up at the Pool of Purification.

These disquieting images leave Yuri with no doubt that
Mt. Hikami houses some kind of horrifying secret.

Yuri takes the Camera Obscura that she found on the mountain
and begins searching for a token that will lead her to Hisoka.{end}

#### 6 ####
After finding a missing persons file on Hisoka's desk,
Yuri realizes Hisoka had been looking for Haruka Momose.

She recalls what Fuyuhi said when they passed the Shrine of Dolls:
"Haruka... She's here."

With this in mind, Yuri heads to the Shrine of Dolls, hoping that
if she finds Haruka, she may just learn of Hisoka's whereabouts
too.{end}

#### 7 ####
After being brought back from the mountain, Haruka
disappeared again. This time, she seemed to be led away
by the ghost of her friend, Fuyuhi.

Yuri recalls one more open case from Hisoka's file:
A missing girl named Miu Hinasaki, who went to
Mt. Hikami in search of her mother.

Yuri takes Miu's token with her and sets out for the mountain,
hoping that the key to all the disappearances will be waiting there.{end}

#### 8 ####
In the course of their investigation, Ren and Rui learn of
Keiji Watarai, a folklorist who settled on Mt. Hikami.

His writings are certain to be a treasure trove of information
about the mountain and its peculiar folklore. Ren and Rui
happen across a video tape that may just indicate the way
to Watarai's residence.{end}

#### 9 ####
Yuri managed to rescue Miu from the Shrine of the Ephemeral,
but obtained no new information about Hisoka.

The only clues she has are a photograph found in the Camera
Obscura and the vision she saw when she touched Hisoka's charm.
These lead Yuri to believe Hisoka is somewhere upstream.

Clinging to this last hope of finding her friend, Yuri heads towards
the Lake of the Departed, located on Mt. Hikami's summit.{end}

#### 10 ####
When Yuri returns from Mt. Hikami's summit,
she quickly collapses from exhaustion.

Meanwhile, Miu is also in an unnaturally deep slumber.

Worried that some unwanted visitors may be on their way,
Ren and his assistant Rui decide to watch over the girls through
the shop's surveillance system.{end}

#### 11 ####
Miu wakes up to discover that Yuri has been taken to Mt. Hikami.

She borrows Yuri's Camera Obscura and heads for the mountain,
against Ren's advice.

She hopes not only to find Yuri, but some clues to her mother's
whereabouts as well.{end}

#### 12 ####
Ren checks the surveillance footage only to discover that Rui has
also been beckoned away to the mountain.

He recalls the dream he had after he fell asleep:
Rui was inside the Veiled House, a.k.a. the Watarai Residence.

Ren knows this is where he must head next.{end}

#### 13 ####
Yuri ponders what she saw at the Lake of the Departed:
Hisoka's shadow vanishing into a thick veil of mist.

She recalls the tall torii gate rising from the lake,
marking the entrance to the Shrine on the Water.

Could Hisoka be in that shrine?
Yuri knows she must find a way across. She goes to investigate
the Shrine of the Ephemeral.{end}

#### 14 ####
Having brought Yuri back from the Lake of the Departed,
Miu stays awhile at the antiques shop.

Convinced her mother, Miku Hinasaki, is somewhere on
Mt. Hikami, Miu knows the only way to find her is to
follow her shadow.

To do so, she needs the help of Yuri's Camera Obscura.{end}

#### 15 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui, Miu, Miku, Hisoka and Yuri all fall into an
unusually deep slumber.

Ren fears that while this persists, the defenseless group
may be vulnerable to attack. Time to get back to those
surveillance cameras.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren knows he must find out what's going on with Mt. Hikami
before something comes to pay a visit...{end}

#### 16 ####
The glow of the Dark Sun fades away and the
sleeping girls regain consciousness.

The mountain calls to our three protagonists.
Their individual mysteries await resolution.{end}

#### 17 ####
Ayane is a ninja from the Mugen Tenshin Ninja Clan's
Hajinmon sect.

Her mission: To search for a missing girl, Tsumugi Katashina,
last seen near Mt. Hikami.

Ayane spins a Purple Thread which should help lead her to the girl.{end}

#### 18 ####
When confronted by spirits from the Netherworld, Ayane is forced
to make a fast retreat from the mountain.

She heads in search of a means to fight her new opponents.{end}

#### 19 ####
The Purple Thread leads Ayane to the Shrine of the Ephemeral
on Mt. Hikami's summit.

She heads inside the old shrine, which seems to
exude darkness itself.{end}

#### 20 ####
Within the Shrine of the Ephemeral, Ayane locates Tsumugi
and rescues her from the Black Water. The next step is
to plan their escape.

Surrounded by evil spirits, Ayane knows she has to think fast.{end}

#### 21 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu, a girl who has been "spirited away,"
awoke in a flooded mansion.

While searching for the exit, she came across a room with
nothing but a large, black box inside.

As the box opened, what emerged from within
was not of this world.

With no one there to hear Miu's scream,
her voice was lost in the mist.{end}

#### 22 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}While learning about shadow reading from Hisoka, Yuri used
the ability to retrieve an album of Postmortem Photographs
from a ruined inn on Mt. Hikami. The album was requested
by a certain Ren Hojo.

As Ren awoke from a bad dream, he found himself
tormented by uncertainty.

Was it really just a dream? Or a suppressed childhood memory?

This question has plagued him for some time.{end}

#### 23 ####
While searching for her friend,
Fuyuhi Himino ended up taking her own life.

Having witnessed Fuyuhi's final moments,
Yuri knows she wasn't alone when she died.
What of that other woman who killed herself in the same way?
Not to mention the mysterious shrine maiden,
sodden from the rain...

Yuri managed to locate Hisoka's Camera Obscura,
along with a charm she always liked to wear.
For now, she must return to the antiques shop alone.{end}

#### 24 ####
The photo album left behind by the innkeeper was put together
by a folklorist who lived on Mt. Hikami. As Ren and Rui
explored the inn and traced the spirit of its owner, a ghost
tried to lure Rui to suicide. Then, through the pouring rain,
an ominous shrine maiden appeared.

Ren and Rui left the mountain with more
questions than when they started.{end}

#### 25 ####
Using the Camera Obscura, Yuri found a number of missing
person case files connected to Mt. Hikami.

She is now more determined than ever
to head back to the mountain and find Hisoka.{end}

#### 26 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri finds the missing Haruka Momose in a reliquary in
a cave beneath the Shrine of Dolls.

She takes the girl back to the shop. Haruka is in no state to
talk and can't explain what happened to her.

That night Haruka is visited by Fuyuhi's ghost,
which takes her back to the mountain.{end}

#### 27 ####
Miu Hinasaki was found in a reliquary within
the Shrine of the Ephemeral.

Yuri attempted to glance the sleeping Miu's memories,
but found the tables turned against her.

It seems Miu also possesses the same
shadow reading abilities as Yuri.{end}

#### 28 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren and Rui set out to find the folklorist's house,
relying on clues from a video recording.

As they passed through the Shrine of Dolls,
the white-haired girl from Ren's dreams appeared.

She asked why he didn't bring her token, then vanished.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren and Rui arrived at the Veiled House, where they
discovered several of Keiji Watarai's writings on the customs
and beliefs surrounding Mt. Hikami.

They escaped the house, only to see it
vanish in a thick veil of mist.{end}

#### 29 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri followed Hisoka's trace to the shore of
the Lake of the Departed, where it vanished into the mist.
In her place, a woman appeared: the same dark presence
seen in Hisoka's photograph. Unable to inflict any damage
with the Camera Obscura, Yuri's only option was to run.

Yuri recalled the outline of a large torii gate over the misty lake.
Could that be where Hisoka was headed?{end}

#### 30 ####
Ren is watching over the sleeping Yuri and Miu on the
surveillance cameras, but he passes out. He has a dream
where he's chasing after Rui. When he wakes up, both Yuri
and Rui are gone. He finds Miu getting ready to leave for
Mt. Hikami, taking Yuri's Camera Obscura with her.
The door shuts behind Miu, leaving a bewildered Ren behind.{end}

#### 31 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}As Yuri waded into the mist over the Lake of the Departed,
she was stopped by Miu.

The distance between the girls seemed to narrow.
Losing their parents at a young age and being able
to see into the souls of others... The girls have more
in common than they may have first realized.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Yuri still hasn't found Hisoka, while Miu still searches
for her mother, Miku.

The eerie dark figure that appeared at the lake may just
hold all the answers. But why does she keep calling out to Yuri?{end}

#### 32 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren found Rui in a reliquary in the Veiled House, only
to be pulled in himself. He awoke in an unfamiliar building.

An old woman dressed in white led Ren to a room in which
Rui was waiting, dressed as a bride. This seemed to be the room
in which weddings between the living and the dead are held.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Rui suddenly changed into a fearsome bride wearing black.
Then, in a flash, they were back in the folklorist's house.

There, they encountered Ren's friend Kazuya, whose own
wedding to a ghost went horribly wrong.

The Veiled House vanished into the mist, with Kazuya still inside.{end}

#### 33 ####
Yuri boarded the Boat of Passage and was taken to
the Shrine on the Water, the final destination for
shrine maidens set to become Pillars.

Yuri found Hisoka inside the shrine and took her safely
back to the antiques shop.

The bond between the two of them grew even stronger.{end}

#### 34 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu finally found Miku on Mt. Hikami, where she had
entered into a Ghost Marriage at the House of Joining.

Miku explained her desperate wish to be reunited with her
beloved, pleading for Miu's forgiveness. 

Miu led her mother away from the mountain
and back to the antiques shop.

Miu and Miku lay side by side and quickly fell into a deep sleep.{end}

#### 35 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren learned of the true purpose of the rituals
performed on Mt. Hikami.

The mountain acts as a boundary between the world of the living
and that of the dead. A place at which the souls of visitors
were returned to the water from which they were born.

Shrine maidens absorbed the memories of the dying, and when
they could take no more, they were sacrificed in reliquaries.

{0E:3:0:2:1}Ghost Marriages served to console and strengthen the souls
of those sacrificed. Wedded couples were thrown into the
darkness that leads to the Netherworld.

Water connects everything.{end}

#### 36 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Having absorbed the painful memories of countless ghosts,
Yuri felt the mountain calling for her. She made her way
toward the Shadowspring, lying beneath the Shrine on the Water.

Awaiting her there was Ose Kurosawa, the Immortal Flower.
As Yuri touched Ose, she shared in her immense pain, suffering,
and solitude.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ose, finally freed from her grief, returned to
the Shadowspring alone.

Yuri left the mountain together with Hisoka. As they reached
the base, a thick mist descended once more on Mt. Hikami,
covering it from view.{end}

#### 37 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Having absorbed the painful memories of countless ghosts,
Yuri felt the mountain calling for her. She made her way
toward the Shadowspring, lying beneath the Shrine on the Water.

Awaiting her there was Ose Kurosawa, the Immortal Flower.
Yuri and Ose shared the same pain, alienation and grief.
Together, they ceased to exist.

They are no longer alone.{end}

#### 38 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren roamed around Mt. Hikami, guided by
the memories of Dr. Kunihiko Aso.

Aso's trail led Ren to the House of Joining, where his own
Ghost Marriage would be held.

There, his chosen bride awaited him. Ren was to be wed
with the bride from the photograph, Ose Kurosawa.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ose finally gained the closure she had longed for,
releasing Ren from the mountain's grasp.{end}

#### 39 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Ren roamed around Mt. Hikami, guided by
the memories of Dr. Kunihiko Aso.

Aso's trail led Ren to the House of Joining, where his own
Ghost Marriage would be held.

There, his chosen bride awaited him. Ren was to be wed with
the white-haired girl from his memory, Shiragiku.
{0E:3:0:2:1}Shiragiku finally gained the closure she had longed for,
releasing Ren from the mountain's grasp.{end}

#### 40 ####
Miu and Miku watched as the Dark Sun sunk into the Black Water.

"I'm glad I didn't take you with me."

Miku's final words resonated with Miu as she watched
her mother fade into the Black Water. Miu was left alone,
bitter tears flowing from her eyes.{end}

#### 41 ####
{0E:3:0:2:1}Miu and Miku watched as the Dark Sun
sunk into the Black Water.

"I'm not going anywhere."

Lies.

Miu awoke to find her mother sleeping next to her.

{0E:3:0:2:1}They embraced, as if each making sure the other was real.
For a moment, Miu felt truly happy. Even if this moment would
turn out to be fleeting...{end}

#### 42 ####
Ayane agreed to look for a missing girl named Tsumugi.

Stealing herself into the abandoned inn on Mt. Hikami,
she was severely wounded by a malicious ghost.

How can she fight off these supernatural foes?
Ayane made her escape, realizing she may need the help of
forbidden magic...{end}

#### 43 ####
Ayane cast a spell on herself, bringing her closer to death.
Enveloped in darkness, she followed a purple thread
connected to her target, Tsumugi.

The thread led her to the Shrine of the Ephemeral,
located on the summit of Mt. Hikami.{end}

#### 44 ####
Ayane searched the Shrine of the Ephemeral.

She located and rescued Tsumugi, who was
being swallowed by the Black Water.

An unsettling presence surrounded the pair.
Beings from the Netherworld were all around.{end}

#### 45 ####
Ayane escaped from Mt. Hikami with Tsumugi.

She left the girl with a simple message:

"The stronger your bonds with others, the stronger
you yourself become."

As Ayane turned to leave, Tsumugi replied:
"I'll...get strong."{end}

